mstToolId, name,dependencyName, type, min, max,selections,description
ina_precision_segment,Analysis threshold,,float,,,,"The number of seconds buffer (float) for counting a true positive (match between the ground truth and MGM output). For example, a 2-second threshold will consider a GT and MGM segment a match if both the start and end times for each fall within 2 seconds of each other."
applause_precision,Analysis threshold,,float,,,,"The number of seconds buffer (float) for counting a true positive (match between the ground truth and MGM output). For example, a 2-second threshold will consider a GT and MGM segment a match if both the start and end times for each fall within 2 seconds of each other."
ner_precision_allEntity_perTool,MGM being tested,,single-select,,,"[""Amazon Comprehend"", ""SpaCy""]",(Amazon Comprehend or SpaCy)
ner_precision_allEntity_perTool,Entity types,MGM being tested,multi-select,,,"[{""Amazon Comprehend"": [""COMMERCIAL_ITEM"", ""DATE"", ""EVENT"", ""LOCATION"", ""ORGANIZATION"", ""OTHER"", ""PERSON"", ""QUANTITY"", ""TITLE""]}, {""SpaCy"": [""PERSON"", ""NORP"", ""FAC"", ""ORG"", ""GPE"", ""LOC"", ""PRODUCT"", ""EVENT"", ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""LAW"", ""LANGUAGE"", ""DATE"", ""TIME"", ""PERCENT"", ""MONEY"", ""QUANTITY"", ""ORDINAL"", ""CARDINAL""]}]","Entity types to include in scoring. If left blank, then all entities will be included."
ner_precision_allEntity_mapped,Entity types,,multi-select,,,"[""CONCEPT"", ""EVENT"", ""LOCATION"", ""ORGANIZATION"", ""PERSON"" , ""DATE""]","Entity types to include in scoring. If left blank, then all entities will be included."
ner_precision_uniqueEntity_perTool,MGM being tested,,single-select,,,"[""Amazon Comprehend"", ""SpaCy""]",(Amazon Comprehend or SpaCy)
ner_precision_uniqueEntity_perTool,Entity types,MGM being tested,multi-select,,,"[{""Amazon Comprehend"": [""COMMERCIAL_ITEM"", ""DATE"", ""EVENT"", ""LOCATION"", ""ORGANIZATION"", ""OTHER"", ""PERSON"", ""QUANTITY"", ""TITLE""]}, {""SpaCy"": [""PERSON"", ""NORP"", ""FAC"", ""ORG"", ""GPE"", ""LOC"", ""PRODUCT"", ""EVENT"", ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""LAW"", ""LANGUAGE"", ""DATE"", ""TIME"", ""PERCENT"", ""MONEY"", ""QUANTITY"", ""ORDINAL"", ""CARDINAL""]}]","Entity types to include in scoring. If left blank, then all entities will be included."
ner_precision_uniqueEntity_mapped,Entity types,,multi-select,,,"[""CONCEPT"", ""EVENT"", ""LOCATION"", ""ORGANIZATION"", ""PERSON"" , ""DATE""]","Entity types to include in scoring. If left blank, then all entities will be included."
shot_precision,Analysis threshold,,float,,,,"The number of seconds buffer (float) for counting a true positive (match between the ground truth and MGM output). For example, a 2-second threshold will consider a GT and MGM segment a match if both the start and end times for each fall within 2 seconds of each other."
face_precision_appearance,Analysis threshold,,float,,,,"The number of seconds buffer (float) for counting a true positive (match between the ground truth and MGM output). For example, a 2-second threshold will consider a GT and MGM segment a match if both the start and end times for each fall within 2 seconds of each other."
vocr_precision_text_time,Analysis threshold,,float,,,,"The number of seconds buffer (float) for counting a true positive (match between the ground truth and MGM output). For example, a 2-second threshold will consider a GT and MGM segment a match if both the start and end times for each fall within 2 seconds of each other."
vocr_precision_time,Analysis threshold,,float,,,,"The number of seconds buffer (float) for counting a true positive (match between the ground truth and MGM output). For example, a 2-second threshold will consider a GT and MGM segment a match if both the start and end times for each fall within 2 seconds of each other."
