mstToolId,name,dependencyName,type,min,max,selections,description,defaultValue,isRequired,unit,shortName
ina_precision_segment,Analysis threshold,,FLOAT,0,10,,"The number of seconds buffer (float) for counting a true positive (match between the ground truth and MGM output). For example, a 2-second threshold will consider a GT and MGM segment a match if both the start and end times for each fall within 2 seconds of each other.",0,,seconds,threshold
applause_precision_segment,Analysis threshold,,FLOAT,0,10,,"The number of seconds buffer (float) for counting a true positive (match between the ground truth and MGM output). For example, a 2-second threshold will consider a GT and MGM segment a match if both the start and end times for each fall within 2 seconds of each other.",0,,seconds,threshold
shot_precision,Analysis threshold,,FLOAT,0,10,,"The number of seconds buffer (float) for counting a true positive (match between the ground truth and MGM output). For example, a 2-second threshold will consider a GT and MGM segment a match if both the start and end times for each fall within 2 seconds of each other.",0,,seconds,threshold
ner_precision_allEntity_perTool,MGM being tested,,SINGLE_SELECT,,,"[""comprehend"", ""spacy""]",(Amazon Comprehend or SpaCy),,TRUE,,tool
ner_precision_allEntity_perTool,Match types,,SINGLE_SELECT,,,"[""Yes"", ""No""]",Whether or not an entity's MGM and ground truth entity types should match for it to count as a true positive.,Yes,,,match-types
ner_precision_allEntity_mapped,Ground truth entities,,SINGLE_SELECT,,,"[""comprehend"", ""spacy"", ""common""]",The entity types used in the ground truth file. AWS Comprehend and SpaCy entities will be automatically converted to the common entity types.,,TRUE,,ground-truth-entities
ner_precision_allEntity_mapped,Match types,,SINGLE_SELECT,,,"[""Yes"", ""No""]",Whether or not an entity's MGM and ground truth entity types should match for it to count as a true positive.,Yes,,,match-types
ner_precision_uniqueEntity_perTool,MGM being tested,,SINGLE_SELECT,,,"[""comprehend"", ""spacy""]",(Amazon Comprehend or SpaCy),,TRUE,,tool
ner_precision_uniqueEntity_perTool,Match types,,SINGLE_SELECT,,,"[""Yes"", ""No""]",Whether or not an entity's MGM and ground truth entity types should match for it to count as a true positive.,Yes,,,match-types
ner_precision_uniqueEntity_mapped,Match types,,SINGLE_SELECT,,,"[""Yes"", ""No""]",Whether or not an entity's MGM and ground truth entity types should match for it to count as a true positive.,Yes,,,match-types
ner_precision_uniqueEntity_mapped,Ground truth entities,,SINGLE_SELECT,,,"[""comprehend"", ""spacy"", ""common""]",The entity types used in the ground truth file. AWS Comprehend and SpaCy entities will be automatically converted to the common entity types.,,TRUE,,ground-truth-entities
ner_precision_allEntity_perTool,Entity types,MGM being tested,MULTI_SELECT,,,"[{""comprehend"": [""COMMERCIAL_ITEM"", ""DATE"", ""EVENT"", ""LOCATION"", ""ORGANIZATION"", ""OTHER"", ""PERSON"", ""QUANTITY"", ""TITLE""]}, {""spacy"": [""PERSON"", ""NORP"", ""FAC"", ""ORG"", ""GPE"", ""LOC"", ""PRODUCT"", ""EVENT"", ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""LAW"", ""LANGUAGE"", ""DATE"", ""TIME"", ""PERCENT"", ""MONEY"", ""QUANTITY"", ""ORDINAL"", ""CARDINAL""]}]","Entity types to include in scoring. If left blank, then all entities will be included.",,,,entity-types
ner_precision_allEntity_mapped,Entity types,,MULTI_SELECT,,,"[""CONCEPT"", ""EVENT"", ""LOCATION"", ""ORG"", ""PERSON"" , ""DATE"", ""NUMBER""]","Entity types to include in scoring. If left blank, then all entities will be included.",,,,entity-types
ner_precision_uniqueEntity_perTool,Entity types,MGM being tested,MULTI_SELECT,,,"[{""comprehend"": [""COMMERCIAL_ITEM"", ""DATE"", ""EVENT"", ""LOCATION"", ""ORGANIZATION"", ""OTHER"", ""PERSON"", ""QUANTITY"", ""TITLE""]}, {""spacy"": [""PERSON"", ""NORP"", ""FAC"", ""ORG"", ""GPE"", ""LOC"", ""PRODUCT"", ""EVENT"", ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""LAW"", ""LANGUAGE"", ""DATE"", ""TIME"", ""PERCENT"", ""MONEY"", ""QUANTITY"", ""ORDINAL"", ""CARDINAL""]}]","Entity types to include in scoring. If left blank, then all entities will be included.",,,,entity-types
ner_precision_uniqueEntity_mapped,Entity types,,MULTI_SELECT,,,"[""CONCEPT"", ""EVENT"", ""LOCATION"", ""ORG"", ""PERSON"" , ""DATE"", ""NUMBER""]","Entity types to include in scoring. If left blank, then all entities will be included.",,,,entity-types
